ping.sg 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy policy

This site is owned and operated by PingDotSG (53105762C) (“Ping.sg”). Ping.sg aims to make your experience online satisfying and secure. This statement governs information you provide to us or we learn from your use of this web site and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share this information.

Traditionally, the process goes through 2 stages.

#### Types of Collected Data 

Ping.sg gathers two types of information about this website’s users:

  * Personal information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions, such as email, survey information, and online registration forms to Ping.sg. Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, home address, company name, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card information such as the credit card number, card verification value, and the billing address. The types and amount of personal information collected for these activities will vary depending on the activity.
  * Ping.sg also gathers non-personal information through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This non-personal information collected includes click-throughs, IP addresses, and usage data. This non-personal information allows us to better tailor our content to site users’ needs.

#### Usage Tracking

We track product usage data and user traffic patterns throughout our site to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our site from the reports and emails we sent to our customers. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and to discourage fraud.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are required to use the Ping.sg service. We use cookies to record current session information. Additionally, if you choose the “remember me” option, you are issued a permanent cookie. A permanent cookie is one that remains on the hard drive after the browser application has been closed.

We also use third party advertisements on Ping.sg to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out some, but not all, of this ad servings at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

#### Use of Collected Data 

We use the personal information about you stored in our member database in various ways. We use the personal information collected to provide you with our products and services. In addition, the personal information collected is used for identification and authentication, billing, and to contact you. Finally, information we gather may be used to otherwise improve our services.

#### Transfer and Information Sharing Policy 

We do not share personal information collected on this web site with third parties for their direct marketing. We provide personal information to trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf.

We does not otherwise share personal information about site users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a user’s request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Ping.sg's interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

If Ping.sg should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merge with another entity, information Ping.sg receives from this Site is a Ping.sg asset and may be transferred.

#### International Visitors and Customers 

This web site is hosted in Singapore. If you are visiting from other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from the Republic of Singapore law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to Singapore which does not have the same data protection laws as your region and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of your personal data to the Republic of Singapore as indicated above.

#### Security

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If Ping.sg learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this web site or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this site. Ping.sg may post a notice on our web site if a security breach occurs. If this happens, you will need a web browser enabling you to view the Ping.sg web site. Ping.sg may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [support@ping.sg](mailto:support@ping.sg)

#### Changes and Updates 

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date on the Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personal Information we collect. Your continued use of this web site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.

#### Contacting Ping.sg 

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@ping.sg](mailto:support@ping.sg)
